getcocoon.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy | Cocoon

It is our goal to provide in plain English, the clearest, most concise, and most accurate privacy policy on the Internet. We are open to your suggestions for any changes we could include to make this more clear.

Our business is to protect your privacy. We do not share your data with anyone unless required by law. Your data belongs to you.  Only you have the key to decrypt your data. If you close your account, no trace of your data is left on our systems.

Outside of Cocoon, on our public website, www.getCocoon.com, we use cookies to understand what information people find valuable, how they found us, and how to improve our website. This information is not connected to you or your account in any way.

Your personal information:  
Inside Cocoon we do not use cookies or track your browsing history. We do not share your information with any third-parties nor do we allow third-parities to place their tracking technologies within the Cocoon service. 

Advertising within Cocoon:  
To help pay for the free Cocoon service, advertisements are shown in Cocoon. Ads that are shown in Cocoon may be based on the page that you are currently visiting but not on your browsing history, cookies or past behavior. If you do not want your non-personal URL information to be used, then you can subscribe to the Cocoon+ product at [https:getcocoon.com/plans](https://getcocoon.com/plans).

If you click on an ad, the advertiser will most likely place a cookie in your Cocoon account, which you can manage like any other cookie a website or advertiser gives you. You can ignore it or delete it as you wish, knowing that Cocoon is still protecting your identity and IP address from advertisers.

Only operational information, such as processing speed or what features are under greatest demand, may be used to ensure Cocoon provides the best possible performance and experience to our users.

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to suggestions or as needed. The most current version will be posted [here](https://getcocoon.com/privacy_policy). If we make any changes to this policy we will notify users via their Cocoon mailslot. Continued use of Cocoon after those changes go into effect signifies agreement to the revised Privacy Policy.

We welcome your feedback. Please contact us with your questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement.

Virtual World Computing  
5383 Hollister Avenue, Suite 150  
Santa Barbara, CA 93111
